A Guide to the Lucy Lee Lancaster Papers, 1915-1989
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
Lucy Lee Lancaster Papers, 1915-1989
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, Blacksburg, Va.
Ms1990-069
44 boxes; 44 cu. ft.
Lucy Lee Lancaster was born in Blacksburg, Virginia in 1905 and lived there until she died in 1989. She was one of the first women admitted to Virginia Agricultural and Mechanical College and Polytechnic Institute (popularly known as VPI), and after graduating in 1925, she went on to earn her MLS from Columbia University Library School. She worked at the VPI library for the rest of her career. The Lancaster papers contain biographical materials, family papers, genealogy research, correspondence with family, friends, and business contacts, membership materials from local organizations, and travel memorabilia from her numerous national and international trips.
Lucy Lee Lancaster
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
The Lancaster papers were received from the estate of Lucy Lee Lancaster in the 1988 and 1989.
Biographical Information
Lucy Lee Lancaster was born in Blacksburg in 1905 and lived there until she died in 1989. She was one of the first women admitted to the previously all-male Virginia Agricultural and Mechanical College and Polytechnic Institute (popularly known as VPI, now known as Virginia Tech). Lancaster graduated in 1925. After graduation she took courses from the New York State Library and later attended Columbia University Library School from which she received a master's degree in library science. Lancaster worked at Virginia Polytechnic Institute library for the rest of her career.
Lancaster was a member of many local organizations and an active member of the VT alumnae society. She was elected as first president of the Blacksburg Junior Women's Club, which formed in 1935. In 1979 she received the Founder's Day Award from Virginia Tech.
Scope and Content
The Lancaster papers document Lucy Lee Lancaster's school careers, community involvement, and her abiding interest in genealogy and travel.
Unprocessed additions to the collection are available on request.
Arrangement
The Lancaster papers are divided into five series.
NOTE: Box and folder locations of materials listed are denoted by numbers separated by a colon following "Box-folder:" Because the Lancaster papers are stored off-site, they must be requested three days in advance of anticipated use. Desired boxes can be identified on this listing and then requested through the library catalog, ADDISON. When requested, they will be delivered to Special Collections for use in the reading room.
Series I, Biographical Materials, is divided into general groupings of information about Lancaster and her family. Materials are not organized at a folder level. Information includes personal items such as class notes from grade school through graduate school, ephemera such as membership cards and poetry, photographs, and materials belonging to other family members. There are several family bibles and photographs. [These were formerly boxes 1-13 of the Personal Biographical Materials grouping.]
Series II, Correspondence, contains personal correspondence as well as work-related materials regarding administration, reference questions, and bibliographies. Correspondence is arranged chronologically. There are also many postcards. Postcards sent to Lancaster are arranged by date, while those she collected as souvenirs are arranged alphabetically by place. [These were formerly boxes 1-14 of the Correspondence grouping.]
Series III, Genealogy Materials, is listed in two subseries but stored alphabetically. While the focus is mostly research about various family members and branches, there is also material about family reunions and general genealogy research and workshops. [These were formerly boxes 1-5 of the Genealogy grouping.]
Series III, Membership Organization Materials, is arranged alphabetically by name of organization. It include papers from many groups in Blacksburg as well as VPI associations. Lancaster often served as secretary in the groups, so minutes and correspondence are present. [These were formerly boxes 1-7 of the Memberships grouping.]
Series IV, Travel Materials, includes notes and diaries from extensive travel that are arranged chronologically. These include initial correspondence sent to inquire about a place, itineraries, journals, receipts for purchases, and photographs. [These were formerly boxes 1-4 of the Travel grouping.]
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Related Material
These two collections also contain some materials related to Lucy Lee Lancaster:
BLACKSBURG [VIRGINIA] ORAL HISTORY PROJECT. RECORDS, 1984-85. 0.2 cu. ft. Project of the University Libraries of Virginia Tech to collect information on the history of Blacksburg, Virginia. Collection contains taped interviews, most with transcripts, of the following Blacksburg residents: Cliff Busby, Georgia Croy, S.H. Kessinger, Lucy Lee Lancaster, George Litton, Howard Price, Carrie T. Sibold, and Ellison A. Smyth. Ms85-005.
UNITED DAUGHTERS OF THE CONFEDERACY, DR. HARVY BLACK CHAPTER. RECORDS, 1862-1999. 3.4 cu. ft. Blacksburg, Virginia chapter (formed 1896) of national organization of Confederate veterans' female descendents. Records include files devoted to local Confederate veterans (including letters of Elisha Epperson, 67th Virginia Infantry), chapter financial records, minute books, membership records, financial records, printed materials and scrapbooks. Membership application for Lucy Lee Lancaster located in Box 3, Folder 3. Ms1990-050.
Index Terms
Persons:
Lancaster, Lucy Lee, 1905-1989
Subjects:
Blacksburg (Va.); Local/Regional History and Appalachian South; Montgomery County (Va.)
Genre and Form Terms:
Photographs
Contents List
- Biographical Materials
  Boxes in this series are not fully organized, and do not have folder-level listings.
  - Clippings and Ephemera (Box 1)
  - Calendars, Journals, and Scrapbooks (Box 2)
  - Grade School, High School, Virginia Polytechnic Institute (VPI) (Box 3)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute (VPI) (Box 4)
  - New York State Library School, Columbia University Library School (Box 5)
  - Library Work (Box 6)
  - Writings (Box 7)
  - Ephemera (Box 8)
  - Photographs (Box 9)
  - Martha (sister), Lucy and William (parents) Lancaster (Box 10)
  - William Lancaster (father) (Box 11-12)
  - Family Bibles (Box 13)
- Correspondence
  - Letters to William Lancaster (father), 1918 (Box-folder 14:5)
  - Letters to Lucy Lee Lancaster
    - 1915-1919 (Box-folder 14:1-7)
    - 1920-1924 (Box-folder 14:8-11)
    - 1925-1929 (Box-folder 14:12-18, 15:19)
    - 1930-1934 (Box-folder 14:18, 15:20-33)
    - 1935-1939 (Box-folder 15:34, 16:35-39)
    - 1940-1944 (Box-folder 16:40-44)
    - 1945-1949 (Box-folder 16:45-53)
    - 1950-1954 (Box-folder 17:54-64)
    - 1955-1959 (Box-folder 17:65-75)
    - 1960-1964 (Box-folder 18:76-91)
    - 1965-1967 (Box-folder 18:92, 19:93-109)
    - 1968-1969 (Box-folder 20:110-123)
    - 1970-1972 (Box-folder 21:124-141, 22:142)
    - 1973-1974 (Box-folder 22:143-150)
    - 1975-1977 (Box-folder 22:150-157)
    - 1978-1979 (Box-folder 22:157-158, 23:159-166)
    - 1980-1983 (Box-folder 23:166-174)
    - 1984-1989 (Box-folder 24:175-183)
    - No date (Box-folder 25:203-211)
  - Letters to Lucy Lee Lancaster and Ester Derring, 1973-1979 (Box-folder 24:184-189)
  - Greeting Cards to Lucy Lee Lancaster
    - Birthday Cards, 1976-1977 and no date (Box-folder 24:190-192)
    - Christmas Cards, no date (Box-folder 24:193-197, 25:198-202)
    - Valentine and Easter Cards, no date (Box-folder 25:212)
  - Postcards to Ester Derring, no date (Box-folder 25:212a)
  - Postcards to Lucy Lee Lancaster
    - 1910s (Box-folder 25:213)
    - 1920s (Box-folder 25:214-216)
    - 1930s (Box-folder 26:217-219)
    - 1940s (Box-folder 26:220-222)
    - 1950s (Box-folder 26:223-231)
    - 1960s (Box-folder 26:232-238)
    - 1970s (Box-folder 26:239-241)
    - 1980s (Box-folder 26:242-243)
    - Roanoke, Virginia (Box-folder 26:244)
  - Souvenir Postcards
    - U.S. Sites and Cities
      - Atlantic City, New Jersey (Box-folder 26:249)
      - Blue Ridge Parkway (Box-folder 26:251)
      - Chicago, Illinois (Box-folder 26:253)
      - The Delta Queen (Box-folder 26:255)
      - Detroit, Michigan (Box-folder 26:256)
      - George Washington's Home, Virginia (Box-folder 26:278)
      - New Orleans, Louisiana (Box-folder 26:266)
      - New York City, New York (Box-folder 26:268)
      - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania (Box-folder 26:271)
      - St. Augustine, Florida (Box-folder 26:274)
      - Washington, D.C. (Box-folder 26:280)
    - U.S. States
      - California (Box-folder 26:252)
      - Colorado (Box-folder 26:254)
      - Florida (Box-folder 26:258)
      - Georgia (Box-folder 26:259)
      - New Mexico (Box-folder 26:265)
      - New York (Box-folder 26:267)
      - North Carolina (Box-folder 26:269)
      - Oregon (Box-folder 26:270)
      - Tennessee (Box-folder 26:275)
      - Texas (Box-folder 26:276)
      - Virginia (Box-folder 26:246, 26:277)
      - West Virginia (Box-folder 26:247)
    - Foreign Countries and Airlines
      - Argentina (Box-folder 26:248)
      - Barbados, West Indies (Box-folder 26:250)
      - England (Box-folder 26:257)
      - Guatemala (Box-folder 26:260)
      - India (Box-folder 26:261)
      - Mexico (Box-folder 26:262)
      - MSA, Asian Airlines (Box-folder 26:264)
      - Quantas Airways, Australia (Box-folder 26:272)
      - Spain (Box-folder 26:273)
      - Thailand (Box-folder 26:245)
      - Virgin Islands (Box-folder 26:279)
    - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 26:263)
  - Unprocessed Correspondence (Box 27)
- Genealogy Materials
  - General Genealogy Research Information
    - Chinese History (Box-folder 28:20)
    - Genealogy by Hugh Watson, The Virginia Gazette (Box-folder 28:46)
    - Genealogy Correspondence
      - General Information (Box-folder 28:47, 29:50)
      - Franklin Bennett (Box-folder 28:48)
      - Colonel Harry Temple (Box-folder 29:49)
    - Genealogy Speech (Box-folder 29:51)
    - Montgomery County Day, 1972 (Box-folder 30:165)
    - National Genealogical Society, Atlanta Conference, 1981 (Box-folder 30:166)
    - National Institute on Genealogical Research, 1976 (Box-folder 30:167)
    - New River Historical Society Seminar, 1976 (Box-folder 30:168)
    - Obituaries - Scrapbook, 1966-1977 (Box-folder 30:170)
    - Salem Seminar on Genealogy, 1978 (Box-folder 30:184)
    - Southwestern Virginia Genealogical Society (Box-folder 31:220)
    - Virginia Appalachian Notes (Box-folder 31:238)
  - Family Research
    - Akers, Louise - Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 28:1)
    - Bailey Family (Box-folder 28:2-3)
    - Baker Family (Box-folder 28:4)
    - Barger Family
      - Notes (Box-folder 28:5-7)
      - Barger Fort (Box-folder 28:8)
      - Journal, June 1924 (Box-folder 28:9)
      - Marriages (Box-folder 28:10)
      - Barger Family Newsletter from G.J.P. Barger (Box-folder 28:11-12)
    - Blankenship, Arlene, and Floyd Payne (Box-folder 28:13)
    - Brown Family (Box-folder 28:14-16)
    - Brown, Michael - Family Record (Box-folder 28:17)
    - Cecil/Darst Family (Box-folder 28:18)
    - Cecil Family (Box-folder 28:19)
    - Clement Family (Box-folder 28:21)
    - Clements Family (Box-folder 28:22)
    - Collinsworth (Box-folder 28:23)
    - Darst (Box-folder 28:24)
    - Dow/Dowe - Family Reunion (Box-folder 28:25)
    - Eakle Family (Box-folder 28:26)
    - Echols Family
      - General Notes (Box-folder 28:27-33)
      - Family Tree (Box-folder 28:34-35)
      - Clippings and Notes (Box-folder 28:36)
      - Echols, John (Box-folder 28:37)
      - Scrapbook Items, Clippings, and Photographs (Box-folder 28:38)
    - Epling Family (Box-folder 28:39)
    - Evans Family (Box-folder 28:40)
    - Fillinger Family - Family Tree and Notes (Box-folder 28:41-42)
    - Fillinger, Sarah Sibold (Box-folder 28:43)
    - Fleming Family - Family Tree (Box-folder 28:44)
    - Garst Family (Box-folder 28:45, 29:52)
    - Hale, Grace - Puzzles (Box-folder 29:53)
    - Harris Family (Box-folder 29:54)
    - Helm Family (Box-folder 29:55)
    - Helm-Lancaster Family Register (Box-folder 29:56)
    - The Huguenot - Abraham, Michaux and Descendents by J.D. Eggleston (Box-folder 29:58)
    - James Family - Reunion Material (Box-folder 29:59)
    - Jones Family
      - General Information - Name, Families, Letters and Notes (Box-folder 29:60-62)
      - Family Reunions
        - Correspondence, 1954-1958 (Box-folder 29:63)
        - Reunion Register 1955-1984 (Box-folder 29:64-65)
        - Letters From Those Not Attending (Box-folder 29:66)
        - General Reunion Materials (Box-folder 29:67)
        - Notices (Box-folder 29:68)
        - Arrangements (Box-folder 29:69)
        - Mailing Lists (Box-folder 29:70)
        - 1957 (Box-folder 29:71)
        - Letters, 1965 (Box-folder 29:72)
        - 1970-1971 (Box-folder 29:73)
        - 1972 (Box-folder 29:74)
        - 1975 (Box-folder 29:75)
        - Remarks on Braun (Brown) Ancestors by Lucy Lee Lancaster, 1976 (Box-folder 29:76)
        - 1981 (Box-folder 29:77)
        - 1982 (Box-folder 29:78)
      - Scrapbook Duplicates - Clippings, Pictures, Invitations (Box-folder 29:79)
      - Census Records (Box-folder 29:80)
      - North Carolina (Box-folder 29:81)
      - Botetourt County, Virginia - Records, Marriages (Box-folder 29:82-83)
      - Craig County, Virginia - Marriages, Births, Census (Box-folder 29:84-86)
      - Floyd County, Virginia (Box-folder 29:87)
      - Greenbrier County and Monroe County, West Virginia - Marriage, Census, Indentures (Box-folder 29:88)
      - Giles County, Virginia - Census, Marriages, Land Records, Death and Birth Records (Box-folder 29:89-93)
      - Chap Jones Family - Correspondence and Notes (Box-folder 29:94)
      - Hiram Tracy Jones - Ancestors, Descendents, Memories (Box-folder 29:95-99, 29:104)
      - H.T. Jones - Biography (Box-folder 29:57)
      - H.T. Jones and Christine Echols - Includes Family Tree (Box-folder 29:100-101, 29:103)
      - H.T. Jones - Family Reunion 1976, 1978, 11985 (Box-folder 29:102)
      - Jacob Jones (Box-folder 29:105-106)
      - Wiley Jones Family - Family Tree and Correspondence (Box-folder 29:107)
      - Miscellaneous, Puzzles, Unconnected, Loose Papers (Box-folder 29:108-112)
    - Kessler Family - Family Tree and Correspondence (Box-folder 29:113-114)
    - Kinzer Family
      - General Information - includes Family Outline, Marriages and Births (Box-folder 29:115; 30:134-140, 30:144)
      - Kentucky (Box-folder 29:123)
      - Pennsylvania (Box-folder 29:126)
      - Tennessee (Box-folder 30:132)
      - Augusta County, Virginia (Box-folder 29:116)
      - Bedford County, Virginia (Box-folder 29:117)
      - Botetourt County, Virginia (Box-folder 29:118)
      - Carroll County, Virginia (Box-folder 29:119)
      - Craig County, Virginia (Box-folder 29:120)
      - Floyd County, Virginia (Box-folder 29:121)
      - Giles County, Virginia (Box-folder 29:122)
      - Lee County, Virginia (Box-folder 29:124)
      - Orange County, Virginia (Box-folder 29:125)
      - Pulaski County, Virginia (Box-folder 29:127)
      - Roanoke City and Roanoke County, Virginia (Box-folder 30:128)
      - Rockingham County, Virginia (Box-folder 30:129)
      - Shenandoah County, Virginia (Box-folder 30:130)
      - Tazewell County, Virginia (Box-folder 30:131)
      - Wythe County, Virginia (Box-folder 30:133)
      - Michael Kinzer - Montgomery County, Virginia (Box-folder 30:141)
      - Michael Kinzer - DAR Membership Attempt by Annie Virginia Anderson Walters (Box-folder 30:142)
      - Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 30:143)
    - Lancaster Family - Family Tree and Notes (Box-folder 30:146)
    - Legrand Family (Box-folder 30:145)
    - Le Grand Family and Allied Families - Notes by Walter Gilliss, 1909 (Box-folder 30:147)
    - Link Family (Box-folder 30:148)
    - Martin Family
      - General Information (Box-folder 30:149-155, 30:163)
      - Records in Giles County, VA (Box-folder 30:156)
      - Records in Montgomery County, VA (Box-folder 30:157)
      - Pennsylvania (Box-folder 30:158)
      - Christian Martin and Other Martins in Southwest Virginia (Box-folder 30:159)
      - Hannah Martin and Michael Surface and Descendents (Box-folder 30:160)
      - John Martin and Mary Helm and Descendents (Box-folder 30:161)
      - Mary Martin and David Price and Descendents (Box-folder 30:162)
    - Michaux Family (Box-folder 30:164)
    - Nosler/Nozler Family (Box-folder 30:169)
    - Payne Family - Family Tree and Notes (Box-folder 30:171)
    - Peterman Family (Box-folder 30:172)
    - Porterfield, Jehu Harlan, and Mary Ann Echols Family Tree (Box-folder 30:174)
    - Price Family Genealogy by J. Taylor Keister and Nannie V. Sibold (Box-folder 30:175)
    - Price Family (Box-folder 30:176)
    - Prillaman Family (Box-folder 30:173)
    - Raines Family (Box-folder 30:177)
    - Reynolds Family - Includes Family Tree (Box-folder 30:178-183)
    - Shorter, Frances - Notes (Box-folder 31:185)
    - Shufflebarger Family (Box-folder 31:186)
    - Sibold Family
      - Family Tree, Clippings, Notes (Box-folder 31:187-188)
      - Deed and Marriage Records (Box-folder 31:189)
      - Family Reunion Notebook, 1955-1979 (Box-folder 31:195)
      - Family Reunion - Letters, 1976 (Box-folder 31:190)
      - Sibold and Link Families (Box-folder 31:191)
      - Sibold Notebook No. 1a - Jacob Franz Sibold's First 6 Children (Box-folder 31:192)
      - Sibold Notebook No. 1b - Jacob Franz Sibold's 7-13th Children (Box-folder 31:201)
      - Sibold Notebook No. 2 - Includes Susan Miller, John Henry Sibold and Mary Catherine Linkous (Box-folder 31:193)
      - Sibold Notebook No. 3 - Descendents of Mary Sibold Robinson (Box-folder 31:194)
      - Scrapbook Duplicates (Box-folder 31:196)
      - Arthur P. Sibold - Personal Papers and Negatives (Box-folder 31:197)
      - Elizabeth Jane Sibold Price (Box-folder 31:198)
      - James William Sibold (Box-folder 31:199)
      - Jefferson Davis Sibold (Box-folder 31:200)
      - John Sibold (1755-1831) (Box-folder 31:202)
      - John Sibold (1790-1845) (Box-folder 31:203)
      - John Henry Sibold (Box-folder 31:204)
      - Margarette Lee Sibold McCormick (Box-folder 31:205)
      - Mary Sibold Robinson (Box-folder 31:206)
      - Mary Catherine Sibold Linkous (Box-folder 31:207)
      - Mary Susan Sibold Huffman (Box-folder 31:208)
      - Susan Sibold Miller (Box-folder 31:209)
      - Thomas Jackson Sibold (Box-folder 31:210)
      - Elizabeth Sibold Schaeffer (Box-folder 31:211)
      - Jacob Franz Sibold (Box-folder 31:212)
      - Harriet Francis Sibold Epling (Box-folder 31:213)
      - John Michael Sibold (Box-folder 31:214)
      - Hannah Katherine Sibold Kinzie (Box-folder 31:215)
      - Sarah Anne Sibold Lucas (Box-folder 31:216)
      - George Washington Sibold (Box-folder 31:217)
    - Snidow Family (Box-folder 31:218)
    - Songer Family (Box-folder 31:219)
    - Surface Family
      - General Information (Box-folder 31:231-235)
      - Deeds from Montgomery County, Virginia (Box-folder 31:229)
      - Family Tree from C.S. Boots (Box-folder 31:230)
      - Surface in Pennsylvania (Box-folder 31:236)
      - Adam Surface (Box-folder 31:221)
      - Christian Surface (Box-folder 31:222)
      - George Surface (Box-folder 31:223)
      - Henry Surface (Box-folder 31:224)
      - Jacob Surface (Box-folder 31:225)
      - John Surface (Box-folder 31:226)
      - Martin Surface (Box-folder 31:227)
      - Michael Surface (Box-folder 31:228)
    - Surface/Zehrfas Family (Box-folder 31:237)
    - Walker Family (Box-folder 31:239-240, 32:241-243)
    - Whittaker Family (Box-folder 32:244)
    - Williams, Anna (Box-folder 32:245)
    - Williams, Lottie - Botetourt County, Virginia, Census (Box-folder 32:246)
    - Wygal Family
      - General Information (Box-folder 32:247-248, 253-254, 257, 259, 261-262)
      - Family Tree (Box-folder 32:255)
      - Wysor Family Related to Wygal (Box-folder 32:256)
      - Adam Wygal (Box-folder 32:249)
      - Margaret Wygal and James Miller Family (Box-folder 32:250)
      - Margaret Miller Wygal (Box-folder 32:251)
      - Sebastian Wygal (Box-folder 32:252)
      - Kentucky (Box-folder 32:257)
      - Maryland (Box-folder 32:260)
      - Pennsylvania (Box-folder 32:263)
      - Bland County, Virginia (Box-folder 32:264)
      - Carroll County, Virginia (Box-folder 32:265)
      - Craig County, Virginia (Box-folder 32:266)
      - Floyd County, Virginia (Box-folder 32:267)
      - Giles County, Virginia (Box-folder 32:268)
      - Lee County, Virginia (Box-folder 32:269)
      - Montgomery County, Virginia (Box-folder 32:270)
      - Pulaski County, Virginia (Box-folder 32:271)
      - Smith County, Virginia (Box-folder 32:272)
      - Tazewell County, Virginia (Box-folder 32:273)
- Membership Organization Materials
  - American Association of Retired Persons (AARP) (Box-folder 33:1-2)
  - American Association of University Professors (Box-folder 33:3)
  - American Association of University Women (AAUW)
    - Bibliographies and Suggested Study Material (Box-folder 33:4)
    - Conventions and Conferences (Box-folder 33:5)
    - General Correspondence (Box-folder 33:6)
    - Correspondence and Procedures for VPI Accreditation (Box-folder 33:7)
    - International Relations Kit and Study Group Material (Box-folder 33:8-9)
    - Memos and Notes (Box-folder 33:10-11)
    - Plan for Public Meetings, Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 33:12)
    - Virginia Division Material (Box-folder 33:13)
    - Workshop, Area IV (Box-folder 33:14)
  - American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU), Membership Card (Box-folder 33:15)
  - American Library Association (ALA), General Information and Cataloging, 1930-1945 (Box-folder 33:16-17)
  - Appalachian Peace Education Center 1930-1945 (Box-folder 33:18)
  - The Archeological Society of Virginia - The New River Valley Chapter, General Information and Archeology and History Scrapbook (Box-folder 33:19-20)
  - The Archeological Society of Virginia, Membership Questionnaire (Box-folder 33:21)
  - The Association for the Preservation of Virginia Antiquities (APVA) (Box-folder 33:22)
  - The Association for the Preservation of Virginia Antiquities (APVA) - Montgomery County Branch, Newsletters and Meeting Notices (Box-folder 33:23)
  - Blacksburg Area Committee for Public Schools, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 33:24-25)
  - Blacksburg Art Association
    - Newsletters and Programs (Box-folder 33:26-27)
    - British Information Service (Reference Division) (Box-folder 33:28)
    - Constitution (Box-folder 33:29)
    - 1956-1957 (Box-folder 33:30)
    - Correspondence, 1958-1970 (Box-folder 33:31-41)
    - Correspondence, no date (Box-folder 33:42)
    - Event Announcements (Box-folder 33:43)
    - History (Box-folder 33:44)
    - Letters to Members (Box-folder 33:45)
    - Members List, 1976 (Box-folder 33:46)
    - Newsletter, 1969 (Box-folder 33:47)
    - Newsletter, 1972 (Box-folder 33:48)
    - Newsletter, 1975-1980 (Box-folder 33:49-54)
    - Newsletter, Miscellaneous (Box-folder 33:55)
    - Notes (Box-folder 33:56)
    - Programs of Art Festivals (Box-folder 34:57)
  - Blacksburg Baptist Church (Box-folder 34:58)
  - Blacksburg Chamber of Commerce, Member Tags, 1966-1975 (Box-folder 34:59)
  - Blacksburg Chamber Music Series, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 34:60)
  - Blacksburg Community Action Committee, Correspondence, 1966 (Box-folder 34:61)
  - Blacksburg Community Park Recreation Development Association (Box-folder 34:62)
  - Blacksburg Consumers Club
    - Materials, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 34:63)